Finding Aid for the Edwin S. Shneidman Papers LSC.0385
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Herman Melville documents, Series 4.
  - Jefferey Berman manuscript Surviving Literary Suicide University of Albany (1 of 2)., 1997. (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Berman, Jeffrey Surviving Literary Suicide University of Albany (2 of 2)., 1997. (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Bibliography of Suicides., undated. (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - The Brothers Mann., 1970s. (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Community Mental Health., 1960s & 1970s. (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Condolence Notes., undated. (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Coroner & Death Certificate Articles., 1800s - 1960s. (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Death Articles., 1960s & 1980s. (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Death certificates v.p. v.d., 1800s & 1900s. (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Death Certificates - Index National Library of Medicine., 1961. (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - Death Certificate History., 1969 - 1973. (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - Death Certificate History., 1969 - 1973. (Box 29, Folder 19)
  - De Sidste Timer., 1945. (Box 29, Folder 20)
  - Dreams., undated. (Box 29, Folder 21)
  - Reprints by Knight Dunlap and Shepherd Ivory Franz., 1922 - 1932. (Box 29, Folder 22)
  - HAM Reprints., 1950s - 1990s. (Box 29, Folder 23)
  - HAM Young Melville Chapter 9., 1970s. (Box 29, Folder 24)
  - Elton Hammond., 1800s. (Box 29, Folder 25)
  - Heard, Gerald., undated. (Box 29, Folder 26)
  - Identity/Personality., 1960s. (Box 29, Folder 27)
  - Iga, mamora Suicide of Mishima Yukio., undated. (Box 29, Folder 28)
  - Leenaaras, Antoon A. Suicide: A Multidimensional Malaise (The Presidential Address) Draft., undated. (Box 29, Folder 29)
  - Life Span Articles., 1984. (Box 29, Folder 30)
  - Litman, Robert E., 1960s. (Box 29, Folder 31)
  - Litman Articles., 1960s. (Box 29, Folder 32)
  - Living Systems., 1965 July. (Box 29, Folder 33)
  - Los Angeles Suicide Prevention Center., 1965. (Box 29, Folder 34)
- Professional and Academic Activities, Series 5.
  - Dept & Course Materials - Harvard., 1959 - 1969. (Box 17, Folder 1)
    includes audiocassette
  - Lifelong Learning, Berkeley., 1967. (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - CRV Committee., 1969. (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Course-related., 1970s. (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Death Course., 1971 Fall. (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Death Summer., 1972 Summer. (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Proposed Program in Thanatology., 1972 September. (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Personnel Action., 1975. (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Thanatology., 1977 Winter. (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Death & Suicide., 1980s. (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - HAM Course., 1980s. (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Lecture Notes., 1982. (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Course Evaluations/Course-related materials., 1983. (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Second Year Psychology Class., 1983 May 26. (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Suicide Reading Packet., 1984. (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - UCLA., 1986 Spring. (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Psych 195 Class/Course notes., 1988 Spring. (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Course Evaluations., 1989 December 7. (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Murray, Henry A. (M.D., Ph.D.) "Dead to the World" - Speech USC,., 1963 October 6. (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - HA Murray Seminar - Perry London (USC)., 1964 Fall. (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Ntl. Legislative Scene., 1965. (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - APA Meeting - Suicide Prevention Around the World., 1965. (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Europe., 1967 July 19 - August 15. (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - APA Materials., 1960s. (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - IVSP., 1968. (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - Time and Suicide., 1968. (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - Soc. Rel. Colloquium., 1969. (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - Meeting: International Congress of Suicide Prevention Roche Laboratories Mr. Edward F. Lawlor., 1969. (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - 5th Int'l Conf. for Suicide Prevention., 1969 June 12. (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - CV Professional Speaking Engagements., 1970s. (Box 17, Folder 30)
  - American Assoc. of Suicidology grant request., 1973. (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - American Association of Suicidology Annual Meeting., 1975. (Box 17, Folder 32)
  - Division 12 - Awardees., 1976. (Box 17, Folder 33)
  - Cancer Prevention Committee - CA Center., 1977. (Box 17, Folder 34)
  - ISAP., 1977. (Box 17, Folder 35)
  - Psychology Examining Committee., 1977 April 16 & 17. (Box 17, Folder 36)
  - Suicide Prevention Talks., 1980s. (Box 17, Folder 37)
  - American Association of Suicidology New York., 1982 April. (Box 17, Folder 38)
  - American Association of Suicidology Dallas., 1983 April. (Box 17, Folder 39)
  - Announcement of Psychotherapy, NY., 1983 November 5 & 6. (Box 17, Folder 40)
  - Alzheimer's Disease Assoc. Seminar., 1983 November 19. (Box 17, Folder 41)
  - APA Symposium - Psych Approaches to Literature., 1985. (Box 17, Folder 42)
  - American Association of Suicidology., 1985. (Box 17, Folder 43)
  - Hemlock Society., 1985. (Box 17, Folder 44)
  - International Congress for Suicide Prevention., 1985. (Box 17, Folder 45)
  - National Committee on Youth Suicide Prevention., 1985 - 1986. (Box 17, Folder 46)
  - American Assoc. of Suicidology., 1986. (Box 17, Folder 47)
  - Tampa., 1986 February 6 & 7. (Box 17, Folder 48)
  - Nat'l. Conference on Youth Suicide., 1986 May 9. (Box 17, Folder 49)
  - Portland, OR., 1986 November 14 - 15. (Box 17, Folder 50)
  - Brown University., 1987 January 13. (Box 17, Folder 51)
  - Arnold Air Society., 1987 February 21. (Box 17, Folder 52)
  - CSPA San Diego., 1987 March 19. (Box 17, Folder 53)
  - NPI., 1987 March 28. (Box 17, Folder 54)
  - Western Psychological Association., 1987 April 23 - 27. (Box 17, Folder 55)
  - APA D. Jacobs., 1987 May. (Box 17, Folder 56)
  - AAS/IASP San Francisco., 1987 May. (Box 17, Folder 57)
  - Newport, CA., 1987 October 16. (Box 17, Folder 58)
  - HAM Symposium, APA., 1994. (Box 17, Folder 59)
  - Professional Association., n.d.. (Box 17, Folder 60)
  - Center for Advanced Study in Behavioral Science., ca. 1965 - 1968. (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Center for Life Threatening Behavior., 1970 - 1974. (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Center for Adv. Study in Behavior Sciences., 1970. (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Grants & Proposals., 1972. (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Center for S of LTB., 1972. (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - UCLA Center for Study & Reduction of Violence., 1973. (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Thanatology Training Project., 1974. (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Cancer Control grant application., ca. 1975. (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Community Cancer Control Los Angeles., 1975 - 1976. (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Center for Advanced Study in the Behavioral Sciences - STANFORD., 1975 - 1977. (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Suicide Prevention Committee., 1981 - 1982. (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Pres. Commission on Ethical Problems in Medicine., 1981. (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - UCLA NPI Planning Committee., 1982. (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - NPI Emeritus Center., 1983 - 1984. (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Miscellaneous Interview of Arthur Groman about Armand Hammer., Undated. (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - HAM Notes., Undated. (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Comprehensive Study of Suicide Notes., Undated. (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Des Moines., 1985 April 18. (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Petition for a Writ of Certiorari to Supreme Court., 1986 October. (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Rita Cowart vs. Mutual Life Insurance., 1987 April 1. (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Scalise (1 of 2)., 1987 June 19. (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Scalise (2 of 2)., 1987 June 19. (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Legal file - suicide consultations - expert witness - Restricted., 1988. (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - Lecture outlines, psychoanalysis articles, M.A.P.s responses, & resumes., 1960s - 1980s. (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - Suicide Brochures., 1960s - 1990s. (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - Death and Suicide., 1970s - 1990s. (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - Life Threatening Behavior., 1970s - 1990s. (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - Suicide Prevention Debate., 1972 April 29. (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - YUFIT - Div. 12., 1980. (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - Retirement Remarks., 1988 June 1. (Box 18, Folder 30)
  - MAJEC Resources JCCA A Collection of Course Ideas and Scholars for Hands on use in JCCA., 1990 Spring. (Box 18, Folder 31)
  - SF Paper SLTB., 1990 - 1993. (Box 18, Folder 32)
- Reference Materials, Series 6.
  - Audiovisual Materials.
    - Death & suicide talks on audiocassette & patient audio reels., 1960s - 1980s. (Box 32)
      Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
      CONTAINS UNPROCESSED AUDIO/AUDIOVISUAL MATERIALS: Audio/audiovisual materials are not currently available for access and will require further processing and assessment. If you have questions about this material please email spec-coll@library.ucla.edu. Box contains 87 audiocassetts and 10 audioreels.
    - Audio reels related to suicide., 1960s. (Box 33)
    - Record, audio reels, & audiocassettes related to suicide., 1960s - 1990s. (Box 34)
      including patient interviews
    - Audio reels of articles, speeches, & POS groups., undated. (Box 35)
    - Audio reels, Videotapes of book recordings., 1970s. (Box 36)
      Audio reels of Psychological Autopsy of Malcolm Melville
    - Psychiatric Interviews, Course Tapes., 1970s. (Box 37)
  - Non ESS Publications.
    - The Management of Sexual Impotence., 1963. (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Mental Health., 1950s & 1960s. (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Misc. Articles not by ESS., late 1800s - early 1900s. (Box 30, Folder 3)
      Early Recognitions
    - Misc. Articles not by ESS., 1940s - 1980s. (Box 30, Folder 4)
      Includes systems theory articles, The Classification of Mental Disorders by Immanuel Kant,
    - Misc. Articles not by ESS., 1949, 1963, 1990. (Box 30, Folder 5)
      Includes Clinical Psychology, Tarawa - A Marine Tribute, Narrative and Self-Concept, Criteria for the Life History
    - Misc. Articles not by ESS., 1950s. (Box 30, Folder 6)
      Includes The American Psychologist & Symposium: Current Aspects of the Problem of Validity
    - Misc. Articles not ESS., 1960s - 1980s. (Box 30, Folder 7)
      Includes suicide articles, Mark Twain's Exhibitionism, Psychache in Context, Forensic Psychiatry, Psycho-Social Forces in the Community
    - Misc. Articles not by ESS., 1960s. (Box 30, Folder 8)
      Includes suicide articles, The Psychoanalytic Forum, Psychiatry & Social Science Review,
    - Misc. Articles not ESS., 1970s. (Box 30, Folder 9)
      Includes the archives, Changing Paradigms in Social Work, & The Existence of Death
    - Misc. articles, etc. not ESS., 1970s. (Box 30, Folder 10)
      Includes Personality, Suicide Among Police, The Homer of the Pacific
    - Misc. Articles not by ESS., 1970s. (Box 30, Folder 11)
      Includes suicide and health articles
    - Misc. Articles not by ESS., 1980s. (Box 30, Folder 12)
      Includes suicide articles & Choosing the Rigth Fictions of Scientific Law
    - Misc. Articles not by ESS., undated. (Box 30, Folder 13)
      Includes suicide, death, health, & philosophy articles
    - Misc Reprints., 1950s. (Box 30, Folder 14)
      Includes Role of a Vicarious Object in Adaptation to Object Loss, Psychological Factors and Reticuloendothelial Disease, Countertransference Reactions to Cancer, Death Notification
    - Misc. Reprints not by ESS., 1970s & 1980s. (Box 30, Folder 15)
      Includes Los Angeles Psychoanalytic Bulletin, draft of Thematic Analysis of Suicide Notes: Pseudo and Real
    - Morgen Thaler., 1945. (Box 30, Folder 16)
      Letzte Aufzeichnungen von Selbstmordern
    - Mourning and melancholia., ca 1916. (Box 30, Folder 17)
    - H.A. Murray Reprints., undated. (Box 30, Folder 18)
    - Old Notes., undated. (Box 30, Folder 19)
    - Other Death Documents., undated. (Box 30, Folder 20)
    - Pavese: This Business of Living., 1961. (Box 30, Folder 21)
    - Personal Journal, Author unknown., 1995. (Box 30, Folder 22)
      written by one of ESS colleagues
    - Philosophy Articles., 1960s. (Box 30, Folder 23)
      Includes Interpretation Within the Metaphor: Further Considerations & Phenomenology and Dynamics of Hoping
    - Psychological Autopsy., undated. (Box 30, Folder 24)
    - Psychology General., 1950s - 1980s. (Box 30, Folder 25)
      Includes The Measurement Problem in Psychology, A Standpoint for the Study of the History of Psychology, Toward a General Theory for the Behavioral Sciences
    - Publications non ESS., 1940s - 1960s. (Box 30, Folder 26)
      Includes Preventive Intervention in Situational Crises, Religion and Suicide, Manual of Diagnostic Psychological Testing
    - Rorschach Cards for Children., 1969. (Box 30, Folder 27)
    - Self-injury., 1966 February. (Box 30, Folder 28)
    - Some Facts about Suicide., undated. (Box 30, Folder 29)
    - St. Christopher's Hospice., 1970s. (Box 30, Folder 30)
    - Suicide and the Unconscious Proofs., 1995. (Box 30, Folder 31)
    - Suicide Articles., 1960s. (Box 30, Folder 32)
    - Suicide Articles., 1970s. (Box 30, Folder 33)
    - Suicide Articles., 1980s. (Box 30, Folder 34)
    - Suicide Articles., undated. (Box 30, Folder 35)
    - Suicide Assessments., undated. (Box 30, Folder 36)
    - Suicide Resources., 1965 September 15. (Box 30, Folder 37)
    - Surveys., 1965. (Box 30, Folder 38)
    - Tripodes/Freedman/ESS., 1976 April 8. (Box 30, Folder 39)
    - Diary - Wallace Baker., 1913. (Box 30, Folder 40)
    - Widowed Articles., 1960s. (Box 30, Folder 41)
    - The Academy., 1976 December. (Box 31, Folder 1)
      Copy of quarterly journal
    - Between Sessions., 1984. (Box 31, Folder 2)
      Softcover print of book
    - A Clinical Study of Widow Bereavement Involving Various Modes of Death., 1979. (Box 31, Folder 3)
      Softcover copy of dissertation
    - Reasoning Patterns in Suicide., 1968 July. (Box 31, Folder 4)
      Printed bound copy
    - Treatment on Modeling a Paranoid Mind., 1981. (Box 31, Folder 5)
      Reprint copy
    - The Wilson Quarterly., 1977 Summer. (Box 31, Folder 6)
      Softcover copy
    - Assorted Suicide Articles & Book Reviews., 1960s & 1970s. (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - Assorted Newspaper Clippings., 1960s, 1970s, & 1990s. (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - Nixon Clippings., 1969. (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - Press Clippings., 1970s - 1990s. (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - Assorted Newspaper Clippings., 1970s & 1980s. (Box 31, Folder 11)
    - Clippings., 1970s & 1980s. (Box 31, Folder 12)
    - Newspaper Clippings., 1971. (Box 31, Folder 13)
    - Finnish newspaper article on ESS and English translation., 1977. (Box 31, Folder 14)
- Suicide Prevention Centers
  - Los Angeles Prevention Center
    - LASPC Groundbreaking announcement., 1962 October 12. (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - LASPC files 1963-1966. (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - LASPC Training manual., undated. (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Suicide Prevention Center Assessment of Suicidal Potentiality., undated. (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Farberow, Norman C. correspondence., 1965-1966. (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - ESS Prevention Center notes., 1965-1969. (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - LASPC Correspondence., 1965-1966. (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - LASPC Financial Report., 1975. (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Board of Directors meeting., 1977. (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - LASPC printed materials., 1965-1967. (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Interview with Dr. Jacques Choron, "My Death"., 1966 and 1968. (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Choron interviews on death., 1966. (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - SPC note cards and 40th anniversary speech., 1960s and 1998 September 12. (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - NIMH National Prevention Center Program
    - Employment paper work for ESS at NIMH Suicide Prevention Center and Mental Health Project Grants Committee meeting., 1965 and 1966. (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Psychiatric and legal aspects of suicide prevention., undated. (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - NIMH Center proposals., undated and 1968. (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - National Institute of Mental Health Center correspondence., 1963-1966. (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - NIMH proposals, approaches, goals, and other correspondence., 1960s. (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - NIMH Suicide Prevention Program., 1966 February 1. (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - NIMH reports and correspondence., 1966-1968. (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - NIMH miscellaneous correspondence and materials., 1966-1985. (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - NIMH Center for Studies of Suicide Prevention., 1967-1968. (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Bert Brown correspondence., 1971-1972. (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - NIMH Training record transcript., c. 1970. (Box 6, Folder 21)
      This goes along with a vinyl record, located in the Audiovisual Series (a copy of the transcript is located there, as well).
    - "The NIMH Center for Studies of Suicide Prevention," by ESS., undated. (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - New SPCs., 1965-1966. (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - NIMH 1986 Task Force (1 of 4). (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - NIMH 1986 Task Force (2 of 4). (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - NIMH 1986 Task Force (3 of 4). (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - NIMH 1986 Task Force (4 of 4). (Box 6, Folder 27)
- Suicide Research
  - . (Box Unknown container 908 for instance of.)
  - MAPS -- "Make A Picture Story" Psychological assessment test, developed by E. Shneidman -- Restricted., 1947. (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - MAPS -- Correspondence on the use of the MAPS test in clinical cases -- Restricted., 1947. (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - MAPS -- Test materials and correspondence -- Restricted., 1947. (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - MAPS -- MAPS sheet -- Restricted., 1948. (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - MAPS -- Project, Psychotic patient profile -- Restricted., 1948 January 26. (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - MAPS -- Project, patient profile -- Restricted., 1947 August 22. (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - MAPS -- Project, patient profile -- Restricted., 1947 July 17. (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - MAPS -- Project, "Normal" patient profile -- Restricted., 1947 August 6. (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - MAPS -- Project, "Normal" patient profile -- Restricted., No date. (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - MAPS -- Project, "Normal" patient profile -- Restricted., 1948 February 6. (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - MAPS -- Project, "Normal" patient profile -- Restricted., 1948 January 27. (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - MAPS -- Project, "Normal" patient profile -- Restricted., 1948 January 3. (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - MAPS -- Project, "Normal" patient profile -- Restricted., 1948 January 24. (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - MAPS -- Project, Patient in-take profiles, multiple -- Restricted., 1947-1948. (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - MAPS -- Project, interviewee files 1-10 -- Restricted., July - August 1947. (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - MAPS -- Project, interviewee files 12-20 -- Restricted., September - November 1947. (Box 1, Folder 35)
    Note: File #11 is not in the collection.
  - MAPS -- Project, interviewee files 21-30 -- Restricted., July 1947 - January 1948. (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - MAPS -- Project, interviewee files 31-40 -- Restricted., August - November 1947. (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - MAPS -- Project, interviewee files 42-50 -- Restricted., November 1947 - February 1948. (Box 1, Folder 38)
    Note: File #41 is not in the collection.
  - Terman Study on Gifted Children questionnaires, multiple participants, and notes - - Restricted., 1951. (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Patient summary sheets (3) [names withheld] -- Restricted., 1959. (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Patient suicidal histories (5) [names withheld] -- Restricted., 1959. (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Patient interview notes by Shneidman [name withheld] -- Restricted., 1952 and 1953. (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Patient interview notes by Shneidman [name withheld] -- Restricted., 1955 and 1957. (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Patterns of Thinking, Subject-completed forms and notes -- Restricted., 1964. (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Ethnographic Validity Study, with Prof. Dwaine Marvick of UCLA -- Restricted., 1965-1966. (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - National Center for Health Statistics correspondence -- Restricted., 1965. (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Alcoholism notes -- Restricted., 1960s. (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Psychological Autopsy of Domenico DiPietro -- Restricted., 1968-1969. (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Domenico DiPietro Interview -- Restricted., 1969. (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Completed Death concept questionnaires, notes, and patient interview -- Restricted., 1966. (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Harvard Death Questionnaires (1 of 3) -- Restricted., 1966. (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Harvard Death Questionnaires (2 of 3) -- Restricted., 1966. (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Harvard Death Questionnaires (3 of 3) -- Restricted., 1966. (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Jews on Death, questionnaire -- Restricted., 1966. (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Research projects: Suicide and Male homosexuals -- Restricted., 1963-1966. (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Grant application and correspondence for "Suicide Potentiality of Patients with Cancer" -- Restricted., 1964-1965. (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Uncategorized notes and assessment forms -- Restricted., 1961-1965. (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Various notes on sleep and suicide -- Restricted., 1965. (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Research files, Demographics -- Restricted., 1969. (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - A Present Day Survey Of Suicide Prevention in Europe -- Restricted., 1961-1962. (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Immolation Suicidal Deaths -- Restricted., 1965. (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Suicide notes -- Restricted., 1966. (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Suicide Prevention in Los Angeles: A Follow-up Study, Alan J. Pollack, MD -- Restricted., 1965. (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Miss APA -- Restricted., 1959. (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Subject numbers 207-212 -- Restricted., Undated. (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Psychology Today Survey -- Restricted., 1970. (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Martin S-D Inventory -- Restricted., 1970. (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Uncategorized notes -- Restricted., 1970. (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous research notes, including Mensa poll -- Restricted., 1970-1971. (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - WERT, Weilgart, John W. assessment tool -- Restricted., 1971 December 30. (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Suicide Research -- Restricted., 1971. (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Patient profile and diary [name withheld] -- Restricted., 1971-1972. (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Marin County Coroner -- Restricted., April 1972. (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Suicide and Failure -- Restricted., 1976. (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Patient diary [name withheld] -- Restricted., 1976. (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Betty Williams mystery death -- Restricted., 1977. (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Suicide Research files -- Restricted., 1970-1985. (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Laetrile, cancer treatment -- Restricted., 1970s. (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Participant Consent forms -- Restricted., 1971-1985. (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Patient Profile, notes and interviews [name withheld] -- Restricted., 1971. (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Patient evaluation questionnaire [name withheld] -- Restricted., 1977. (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Death notes and suicide information -- Restricted., 1975-1976. (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Patient Care Associate Program -- Restricted., 1977. (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Statement of the synthesis on suicide notes and death -- Restricted., undated. (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Simulated suicide notes and life history data -- Restricted., undated. (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Suicide notes and life histories [name withheld] -- Restricted., 1970-1976. (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Patient profile, notes and record [name withheld] -- Restricted., 1975. (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Suicidal reflections of immolation, correspondence -- Restricted., 1974 June 7. (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Patient interview [name withheld] -- Restricted., undated. (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Appendix, Suicide Notes -- Restricted., 1968-1973. (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Suicide notes, patient notes from Dr. Bill Worden [name withheld] -- Restricted., 1969. (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Patient suicide profile [name withheld] -- Restricted., 1971-1972. (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Suicide notes, Russian poets -- Restricted., undated. (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Minnesota Multiphasic Personality Inventory (MMPI), blank -- Restricted., undated. (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Patient profile, notes, correspondence [name withheld] -- Restricted., 1973-1975. (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Phone messages with patient names -- Restricted., 1974. (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Patient notes [name withheld] -- Restricted., undated. (Box 3, Folder 36)